

Contact

- Po Box 222 Uaq, Uae
- mohammedsaidali69@gmail.com
- https://dev-saeedali.netlify.app
- in www.linkedin.com/in/moham med-said-ali
- (\$\) 971-54-767-9616

Education

Brillianz Group

Certificate of Bachelor of commerce 2020- 2022

The English School

Certificate of Class XII 2016 - 2018

The New Indian School

Certificate of Class X March - 2016

Technical Skills

HTML5

CSS

Javascript

Bootstrap

Sass

React Js

Mohammed Said Ali

Front End Web Developer

Work Experience

Accounts Assistant

Amrut Pure Drinking Water I Al Salamah Uaq

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

- Received and verified employees' expense reports to cut expense reimbursements.
- Coded all transactions according to the internal company system to avoid errors.
- Prepared financial reports for senior managers to aid in the budget processes and support accurate decision making.
- Compiled data from cashiers, balanced drawers and prepared daily deposits.

Cutomer Service

Feb 2020 - May 2021

Cititrans Logistics L.L.C | Sharjah

- Placed outbound calls to existing members to provide additional consultation on products and services.
- Responded to customer questions and complaints and documented consumer communications.
- Researched assistance requested and offered accurate information to resolve issues and respond to inquiries.
- Communicated and followed up with prospective members via phone or email to process pending account applications.
- Addressed customer concerns and complaints and resolved issues promptly.

Languages Known

- > Malayalam
- > Hindi
- ➤ English

Summary

Self-Taught Front end developer with more than 1 year experience working with Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap, Sass and React js. Highely adept in both independent and collaborative projects, with an emphasis on landing page and website development.

Reference

Sameer

Hr Manager, Cititrans Logistics LLC

Phone: 971-56-547-1599

Email: Shameerkp613@gmail.com